export const PROBLEM_OF_MONTH_2020 = [
    {
        month: "January",
        year: 2020,
        question: "1912q.pdf",
        solution: "2001a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Muti Kara", affiliation: "Ankara Atatürk Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Harold Bögeholz", affiliation: "Melbourne, Australia" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "February",
        year: 2020,
        question: "2001q.pdf",
        solution: "2002a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Ramil Jabiyev", affiliation: "Bilkent Üniversitesi, Ankara" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "March",
        year: 2020,
        question: "2002q.pdf",
        solution: "2003a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Emirhan Yağcıoğlu", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Matematik ve Fen Bilimleri Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Sena Başaran", affiliation: "İstanbul Erkek Lisesi" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "April",
        year: 2020,
        question: "2003q.pdf",
        solution: "2004a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Ruben Victor Cohen", affiliation: "Argentina" },
            { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "UNIST, South Korea" },
            { name: "Şevket Onur Yılmaz", affiliation: "Kabataş Erkek Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Ahmet Yüksel", affiliation: "Efeler, Aydın" },
            { name: "Mehmet Akif Yazıcılar", affiliation: "Bilkent alumnus" },
            { name: "Alper Balcı", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Lim Chang Kiat", affiliation: "Malaysia" },
            { name: "Steffen Weber", affiliation: "Ismaning, Germany" },
            { name: "Kee-Wai Lau", affiliation: "Hong Kong, China" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "M. Lütfi Yarar", affiliation: "İstanbul Technical University" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "May",
        year: 2020,
        question: "2004q.pdf",
        solution: "2005a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "UNIST, South Korea" },
            { name: "Alper Balcı", affiliation: "Middle East Technical University" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "M. Lütfi Yarar", affiliation: "İstanbul Technical University" },
            { name: "Şevket Onur Yılmaz", affiliation: "Kabataş Erkek Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Mehmet Özgün Cihangir", affiliation: "Middle East Technical University" },
            { name: "Emirhan Yağcıoğlu", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Matematik ve Fen Bilimleri Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Tan Özalp", affiliation: "Middle East Technical University" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Özel Antalya Bil Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Chui Tsz Fung", affiliation: "Hong Kong" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "John Wright", affiliation: "Brooklyn, New York, USA" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "June",
        year: 2020,
        question: "2005q.pdf",
        solution: "2006a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "July-August",
        year: 2020,
        question: "2006q.pdf",
        solution: "2008a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Haruhisa Oda", affiliation: "University of Tokyo, Japan" },
            { name: "İbrahim Berkay Ceylan", affiliation: "Giresun Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Alper Balcı", affiliation: "ODTÜ" },
            { name: "Chui Tsz Fung", affiliation: "Hong Kong" },
            { name: "Mehmet Özgün Cihangir", affiliation: "ODTÜ" },
            { name: "Kadyr Annabayev", affiliation: "Turkmen State Institute of Architecture and Construction, Aşkabat" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Ahmed Said Gençkol", affiliation: "Ankara Atatürk Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Emirhan Yağcıoğlu", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Matematik ve Fen Bilimleri Anadolu Lisesi" },
            { name: "Mehmet Koca", affiliation: "Denizli Koleji" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "September",
        year: 2020,
        question: "2008q.pdf",
        solution: "2009a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Alper Balcı", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Muhammed Kızılkaya", affiliation: "Kabataş Erkek Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "İstanbul" },
            { name: "Henrik Åberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "Şevket Onur Yılmaz", affiliation: "Kabataş Erkek Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Mehmet Özgün Cihangir", affiliation: "METU, Ankara" },
            { name: "Mountassir Farid", affiliation: "Awalee Consulting Paris, France" },
            { name: "Tan Özalp", affiliation: "METU, Ankara" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Antalya" },
            { name: "Murat Apaydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Mukammet Batyrov", affiliation: "Saparmurat Turkmenbashy School, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Chui Tsz Fung", affiliation: "Hong Kong, China" },
            { name: "Barış Koyuncu", affiliation: "Özel ENKA Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Berke Yavuz", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Steffen Weber", affiliation: "Ismaning, Germany" },
            { name: "Constantinos Calomitsini", affiliation: "Yanya University, Greece" },
            { name: "Mustafa Kaynak", affiliation: "Giresun University" },
            { name: "Haruhisa Oda", affiliation: "The University of Tokyo, Japan" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Cristian Baeza Miranda", affiliation: "Pontifical Catholic University of Chile" },
            { name: "İsmet Avar", affiliation: "Buca Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Kee-Wai Lau", affiliation: "Hong Kong, China" },
            { name: "Amir Alakbarli", affiliation: "Baku, Azerbaijan" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Berk Tınaz", affiliation: "Bilkent University alumni" },
            { name: "Arsen Berk Tekdaş", affiliation: "METU, Ankara" },
            { name: "Abdulkadir Tanrıverdi", affiliation: "Eskişehir" },
            { name: "Jepbar Asgarov", affiliation: "" },
            { name: "Serdar Hocayev", affiliation: "Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Halil İbrahim Dokuyucu", affiliation: "Trabzon" },
            { name: "Merdangeldi Bayramov", affiliation: "Turkmen State University, Ashgabat" },
            { name: "Nihat Habizada", affiliation: "Baku Higher Oil School, Azerbaijan" },
            { name: "Mesut Yiğit", affiliation: "Jackson Laboratory, Farmington, USA" },
            { name: "Mehran Hosseini-Pishrobat", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Ahmet Yüksel", affiliation: "Aydın" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "October",
        year: 2020,
        question: "2009q.pdf",
        solution: "2010a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Barış Koyuncu", affiliation: "Özel Enka Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Berke Yavuz", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Halil İbrahim Kanpak", affiliation: "Kütahya Nafi Güral Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "November",
        year: 2020,
        question: "2010q.pdf",
        solution: "2011a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Barış Koyuncu", affiliation: "Özel Enka Lisesi, İstanbul" },
            { name: "Merdangeldi Bayramov", affiliation: "Turkmen State University, Ashgabat" },
            { name: "Mümtaz Ulaş Keskin", affiliation: "Antalya" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Muhammetmyrat Gocmyradov", affiliation: "Saparmurat Turkmenbashy School, Turkmenistan" }
        ]
    },

    {
        month: "December",
        year: 2020,
        question: "2011q.pdf",
        solution: "2012a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
            { name: "Chui Tsz Fung", affiliation: "Hong Kong" },
            { name: "Steffen Weber", affiliation: "Ismaning, Germany" },
            { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
            { name: "İbrahim Berkay Ceylan", affiliation: "Giresun Fen Lisesi" },
            { name: "Jepbar Asgarov", affiliation: "Hitrowka, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Tan Özalp", affiliation: "Middle East Technical University, Ankara" },
            { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Muhammed İkbal Ulvi", affiliation: "Middle East Technical University, Ankara" },
            { name: "Kadyr Annabayev", affiliation: "Turkmen State Institute of Architecture and Construction, Turkmenistan" },
            { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
            { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Omar Sonebi", affiliation: "Lycee technique Settat, Casablanca, Morocco" },
            { name: "Enes Kocabey", affiliation: "Google, Mountain View, USA" },
            { name: "Kipp Johnson", affiliation: "Oregon, USA" }
        ]
    }
];
